我... 不... 你... 电邮...
I didn't understand your e-mail.
你能再说一次吗  你说话断断续续
Uh, can you repeat that? You're breaking up.
我... 看不懂... 你的电邮...
I didn't understand your e-mail.
我得加入点巧思
Ah. Yeah, I had to get a little creative
因为我笔记本电脑S  R  M键坏了
because the S, R and M keys on my laptop stopped working.
"亲爱滴阿米  能拜偷你
"Deaw Aby, could you pleathe dwive be
他把s用th  r用w   m用b代替
原句是"明天有空载我去火车玩具店吗"
宁天有空载偶企火车玩鸡店吗"
to the twain thtowe thubtibe tobowow?"
你同意吗
So, is that a yes?
谢尔顿  你为什么不买台新电脑
Sheldon, why don't you get a new computer?
你知道你那台该淘汰了
You know that one's out-of-date.
但我喜欢这台电脑
Oh, but I like this computer.
画质越来越烂  声音越来越断
The video is failing, and the sound is cutting out.
抱歉  我没听到你说的
I'm sorry, I didn't get that.
显卡要挂了
The video is failing,
声卡要死了
and the sound is cutting out.
抱歉  再一次  声音断断续续
I'm sorry, one more time. The sound is cutting out.
我看不清
I can't read that!
显卡不行了
The video is failing!
买... 新电...
Get a new computer.
啥
What?
买... 电脑...
Get a new computer.
虾密
What?!
-喂  -快买个新电脑
- Hello? - Get a new computer!
这挺酷啊
This is cool.
我们上一次一起合作造东西是什么时候
When was the last time you and I built something together?
科学方面的东西  大概是一年多前
Scientifically? A little over a year ago.
乐高积木  上周在我房里
LEGOs? Last week in my room.
如果有一个"一摸就解体的
If there was a Nobel Prize for Millennium Falcons
千禧年猎鹰号乐高"诺贝尔奖  我们一定赢
that fall apart when you pick them up, we'd be set.
两位
Hey, guys!
你们怎么来了
What are you doing here?
我们听说这里有性感科学家
We heard there were some sexy scientists
-整个周末在努力工作  -是啊
- working hard all weekend. - Yeah,
所以带午餐来给你们  然后去找性感科学家
so we brought you some lunch and we are gonna go look for 'em.
汤  三明治  加羞辱
Soup, sandwiches and emasculation,
就像我妈做的午餐一样
just like my mom used to make.
情况如何
So, how's it goin'?
还行  进度有些慢
Good. Slow.
有很多无聊的前置工作得做  但只要弄好这部分
There's a lot of tedious setup, but once we get through that
进度应该就会加快
it should go quicker.
有什么事我们能帮忙吗
Is there anything we can do to help?
其实这部分不需要什么技术性
You know what, this part isn't that technical.
你们还真能帮上忙
You actually could.
真的吗  被你抓到我胡扯  那我认命吧
Wow, really? Called my bluff. All righty then.
我们真能帮上忙吗
Can we really help?
我们焊接这些板的时候  如果你们
While we finish soldering these boards, it'd be great
可以帮忙用铁氟龙胶带缠住这些管件就太好了
if you guys could wrap these pipe fittings with Teflon tape.
我缠一个给你们看
I'll show you how to do one.
你觉得如果你们
Hey, w-wouldn't it be funny
辛辛苦苦干了这么多年
if after all your years of hard work,
最后是我取得科学上突破  会不会很好笑
I'm the one who makes a scientific breakthrough?
他不觉得好笑
He doesn't think that's funny.
我以最快的速度赶来了
I got here as quickly as I could.
你来晚了
You're too late.
谢尔顿  这太智障
Sheldon, this is silly.
你的实验室猴子死掉的时候  你也很伤心啊
You got emotional when that lab monkey died.
那只猴子用手语对我说过"我爱你"
That lab monkey told me he loved me in sign language.
这下好了
Great.
这曲子要卡在我脑子里一整天了
Now I'm gonna have that song in my head all day.
请节哀顺变
Look, I'm-I'm sorry for your loss,
但我有个东西
but I think I have something
能让你开心起来
that might make you feel better.
我给你买了台新电脑
I got you a new computer!
你怎么能这么做
How could you do that?
做什么
Do what?
选购新笔电是非常私人的仪式
Choosing a new laptop is an incredibly personal ritual.
你夺走了我数周的脑海里烦心苦恼
You have taken away weeks of agonizing thought,
各种无聊的搜索研究
tedious research,
多个被我的犹豫不决所填满的无眠之夜...
sleepless nights filled with indecision. I j...
难道我今天失去的还不够多吗
Haven't I lost enough today?
店里的那个店员说这台很赞啊
Well, the guy at the store said this one is great.
那个店员咩
Oh! Oh, the guy!
原谅小的
Oh, pardon me.
我不知道是"那个店员"说的
I-I didn't realize you'd spoken to the guy.
告诉我
Yeah, tell me,
那个店员选了4K显示屏
did the guy choose one with a 4K display
还带有雷电接口的吗
and a Thunderbolt port?
-是的  -是吗
- Yes. - Yeah?
那这个店员有没有
D-Did the guy make sure
确保这台是有1TB固态硬盘的呢
that this has a one-terabyte solid-state drive?
-是的  -是吗
- Yes. - Yeah?
他是不是就是科罗拉多电脑店的里克呢
Oh, well, was this guy Rick from Computer Solutions on Colorado?
是的
Yes.
好吧  他的确是很懂行
Yeah, well, he does know his stuff.
把主体用反光带包起来之后
After you wrap the body in reflective tape,
末端用铁氟龙胶带缠住  这样封口才会紧密
the ends get Teflon tape so we can get a tight seal.
-这样吗  -完美
- Like this? - Yeah, perfect.
手指小巧灵活的人干这个比较有优势
And it helps to have small, delicate fingers.
所以你要是没有我跟霍华德快
So don't be discouraged if you can't do it as fast
不要太气馁哦
as me and Howard.
我们好像没有足够焊料
I don't know if we have enough solder
来焊住这些电路板
to finish these circuit boards.
昨天不好有剩一整个焊料线轴吗
We had a full spool yesterday.
我能说啥
What can I say,
小爷性子野  焊接时更野
I play hard, I solder even harder.
有时候他在家光膀子焊接东西
Sometimes he solders at home with his shirt off.
简直像啤酒广告般狂野
It's like a beer commercial.
我们得跑一趟五金店了
Well, we got to make a run to the hardware store.
你怎么好意思自称科学家  结果没焊料
How can you call yourself a scientist and run out of solder?
这事说起来好笑
Well, funny story.
我们有很多60/40比例的锡铅焊料
So, we have plenty of the 60/40 tin-to-lead ratio solder,
但那个线轴看起来跟63/37的很像...
but the spools look a lot like the 63/37 tin-to...
宝贝  宝贝  你先停停
Honey, honey, honey, let me stop you.
这不是什么好笑的事
That is-is not a funny story.
你想跟我们一起来吗
You want to come with us?
我正开始进入节奏呢
I'm kind of getting into the groove here.
你们去店里买东西
Yeah, you guys run to the store
然后换女人来掌握科学吧
and let the women handle the science for a change.
行
Okay.
我们会尽快回来
We'll be back as soon as we can.
所以  什么...
Okay, so what...
是焊料
is solder?
我想我该先设置电脑
I suppose I should set this up.
还是你要把这份乐趣也剥夺掉啊
Or would you like to rob me of that, too?
不许闹了  否则我要开始把有W的单词
Knock it off or I'll start making W-H sounds
都念出WH的音
for words that just have a W.
你才不会
You wouldn't.
我"嘿"
"Hwatch" Me.
好吧  对不起
Fine. I'm sorry.
谢谢你如此贴心的礼物
Thank you for the thoughtful gift.
我真的很感激
I really do appreciate it.
你也知道  我对我的旧电脑感情很深
As you know, I had become attached to my old laptop.
但我相信  假以时日我会喜欢上...
But I'm sure, in time, that this one will...
我了个妈呀
Jeepers creepers,
这开机也太快了吧
that started up fast!
我就猜你会喜欢
I thought you might like it.
瞧瞧这4K的分辨率
Look at the 4K resolution.
下次我们视频的时候  我要数数
Next time we Skype, I'm gonna count
你到底有几根鼻毛
all those nostril hairs.
或者你可以凝视我的双眼啊
Or you could just look into my eyes.
但你只有两只眼睛啊
But you only have two eyes.
但鼻毛却有好多好多
You got a lot of nostril hairs.
算了  你开心就好
Well, you know, as long as you're happy.
超开心的
I am.
里克说你可以把旧电脑拿过去回收
And Rick said you could bring in your old one to recycle it.
不了  多谢提醒
Oh. Uh, no, no, no, thank you.
但他说回收可以换积分
Oh, but he said you can get store credit.
不用  我不想送去回收
Well, no, I just... I-I don't want to recycle it.
我也不想要积分
And I don't want store credit.
但你为什么不...
But why wouldn't...
我们能换个话题吗
Can we please change the subject?
好吧
O-Okay.
不如我们来谈谈  你态度为什么变这么奇怪
How 'bout we change it to why you're being weird about this?
我的态度才不奇怪
I'm not being weird.
只是很难解释清楚
It's hard to explain.
谢尔顿  实话实话就好啦
Sheldon, just tell me.
可能带你去看更直观
It might be easier to show you.
好吧
Okay.
我们得坐你的车去
We'd have to take your car.
行
All right.
你还得签一份保密协议
And I'm gonna need you to sign a nondisclosure agreement.
我们滚床单前  我也签过一份
Well, I signed one before we slept together.
现在再签一份有何不可
Why not now?
佩妮说她们觉得倒腾原型挺有趣的
Penny says they're having fun working on the prototype.
还记得以前她觉得有趣的是
Remember when her fun was
夜店和喝酒游戏吗
nightclubs and drinking games?
记得  我用超慢速降低她标准
I know. I'm lowering the bar so slowly.
明年的这个时候  她会觉得收藏硬币很有趣
This time next year she'll have a coin collection.
请留步
Excuse me.
两位有兴趣免费观看即将上映的电影吗
You guys interested in a free screening of an upcoming movie?
抱歉  我们没时间
Oh. Sorry, we can't.
等等  是什么电影
Well, hang on. What movie is it?
这我不能说  但主演有威尔·史密斯
Oh, I can't tell you. But it does star Will Smith.
慢着
Wait.
我敢说一定是《X特遣队》
I bet it's Suicide Squad.
我们去看吧
Let's check it out.
那我们的老婆怎么办
What about the girls?
佩妮不是说她们挺开心的吗
Penny just said they're having fun.
讲真  你想一下午都耗在
Honestly, you want to wrap tape around
用胶带缠接管件上吗
a bunch of pipe fittings all afternoon?
好吧  那就看吧
Okay, we'll take 'em.
好
Okay.
但我发誓
But, I swear,
如果是威尔·史密斯主演的《鲨鱼黑帮2》
if it's Will Smith in Shark Tale 2,
2004年由威尔·史密斯配音的动画电影
风评并不佳
那它最好不要比第一部还烂
it better be at least as good as the original.
真是难以置信
I mean, it's crazy, isn't it?
我从家乡搬来这里是为了当女演员
I moved here from Nebraska to be an actress,
而我现在坐在加州理工的工程实验室
and now I'm sitting in an engineering lab at Caltech
帮忙建一个高科技导向系统的原型
helping to build a prototype for a high-tech guidance system.
的确难以置信
It is crazy.
更让人难以置信的是  我已经弄好14个了
It's also crazy that I've made 14 of these
你才弄好3个
and you've made three.
你们老公都去哪儿了
Hey. Where are the guys?
他们出去买焊料了
Oh, they went to the store to get solder,
就是那种能用火熔化做科学东西的金属
which is metal you melt to make science things.
话说你怎么周末也上班啊
Since when do you work on weekends?
我是一位天体物理学家
I'm an astrophysicist.
星星可是365天全年无休哟
The stars don't take a day off.
你是在家寂寞  没人跟你玩吧
You were home alone and had no one to play with?
清洁女工在  但她不喜欢我
Well, the cleaning lady was there, but she doesn't like me.
需要帮忙吗
You need any help?
有"闪电树懒"  速度"飕飕"的
Not with Lightning McQueen here.
我们来就行
I think we're good.
好吧  那就好
Okay. That's cool.
人人都有份参与  唯独我除外
I guess everybody's involved in this project but me.
那我走啦
So... see ya.
我觉得好内疚
I feel bad.
我们要让他留下来吗
Should we have asked him to stay?
要
Yes.
拜托你能告诉我  我们要去哪里吗
Will you please tell me where we're going?
不行  有需要我会告诉你的
Sorry, you're on a need-to-know basis.
我开着这辆车
I'm driving the car.
我需要知道
I need to know.
对[右]
Right.
我们这是要去哪儿
So where are we going?
我是叫你往"右"拐  结果你开过了
No, I meant turn right, and you missed it.
也许你真的需要知道
Maybe you do need to know.
我们要怎么对自己老婆说呢
What are we gonna tell the girls?
这都不是事儿
It's not a problem.
我是说不撒谎的话
I mean without lying.
现在你把这变成大事了
And now you've made it a problem.
拜托  咱俩可是智商超群的人
Come on. We're a couple of smart guys.
一定能想出一个既不破坏我们形象
I'm sure we can come up with a way to explain this
又能合理解释的办法
that doesn't make us look bad.
他们俩为了焊料一路开到圣贝纳迪诺
The boys had to drive all the way to San Bernardino
结果在路上爆胎了
for the solder and got a flat.
她们相信了
They bought it.
不过我们必须得在回家前把备胎换上
But we're gonna have to put the spare on before we go back.
你还真在行啊
Oh, you're good at this.
我是撒谎老手了
Well, I lie a lot.
欢迎各位
Hey, guys, thank you
参加我们今天的试映会
for being a part of our test screening.
你们将成为《X特遣队》的首批观众
You're about to be one of the first audiences to see Suicide Squad.
你说得对
You were right.
我一直跟你说
Oh, I keep telling you--
坏人有好报
good things happen to bad people.
电影即将开始  祝观影愉快
Uh, we're gonna get started in a couple minutes. Enjoy.
你给谁发短信呢
Who are you texting?
拉杰  他特别想看这部电影
Raj. He really wants to see this movie.
他肯定赶不上了
Oh, he'll never make it in time.
我知道  所以我才故意折磨他一下
I know. I want to make him feel bad.
"哈哈  我和莱纳德要看《X特遣队》了
"Ha, ha. Leonard and I are about to see Suicide Squad.
剧透警告  下次见面就是我剧透之时"
Spoiler alert: when I see you I'm gonna spoil it."
你真是个好朋友
You're a good friend.
好了
Okay.
两位女士可以暂时离开一下房间吗
Would you ladies please leave the room for a moment?
为什么
Why?
我要用生殖器把他们的原型机全都蹭一遍
I need to rub my genitals on their prototype.
出什么事了
What's going on?
莱纳德和霍华德不是车爆胎
Leonard and Howard don't have a flat.
他俩一起去看电影了  你们看
They went to the movies. Look.
-小兔崽子  -真他妈不敢相信
- Son of a bitch. - Un-freakin' believable.
我要让他们知道
You know what? I'm gonna let them know
我和你俩在一起  让他们像被抓奸在床
that I'm here with you and that they're busted.
不  别这么做
No. You know what? Don't. Don't.
就让他们以为自己成功骗过了我们
Let's let them think they're getting away with it.
对  看看他们自掘坟墓能掘多深
Yeah, let's see how deep a hole they can dig for themselves.
有意思
Interesting.
虽然比不上在低温恒温器蹭蛋蛋
I mean, it's not testicles on a cryostat,
但我喜欢
but I like it.
你怎么会有一个储藏仓库
Why do you have a storage unit?
不急
Just wait.
你已经租了多久了
How long have you had it?
不急
Just wait.
需要我帮你拿电脑吗
Do you want me to hold that computer?
不急...好呀  谢谢你
Just wai... You know what? Actually, yes, thank you.
欢迎来到我的耻辱之堡
Welcome to my Fortress of Shame.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这都是些什么啊
What-what am I looking at?
这是我曾经拥有的每一件东西
It's basically everything I've ever owned.
每一本书  每一件T恤
Um, every book, every T-shirt,
每一样坏掉的电子产品
every piece of broken electronics.
所有的一切都在这里
Just... all of it.
所有的一切吗
All of it?
我还有一个塑料封口袋
I have a Ziploc bag
用来装我所有用过的塑料封口袋
filled with all my old Ziploc bags.
好吧
Okay.
我要告诉你
I would like to tell you that
这里的一切没什么好羞愧的
there is nothing here to be ashamed of.
我需要一分钟来好好消化一下
So I'm gonna need a minute.
等他们回来我们该作何反应呢
All right, how are we gonna play this when they return?
我知道
I know.
你们俩应该跟我疯狂亲热
You guys should totally be making out with me.
亲爱的  我知道你觉得这种玩笑很好笑
Sweetie, I know you think jokes like that are funny,
但你觉得自己真的有能力
but do you really think you could handle
能驾驭得住我俩吗
making out with both of us?
不  女王
No, ma'am.
好了好了  这个如何
Okay. Okay, how about this?
他们不知道你和我们在一起
They don't know you're here with us,
所以你就藏在这个柜子里
so you hide in the closet.
等他们回来
When they show up,
我们先听听他们编造出来的鬼故事
we'll hear whatever their dumb story is about where they were,
假装相信他们
we'll pretend to believe them,
等他们以为自己成功骗过去的时候
and just when they think they got away with it,
你就跳出来
you jump out.
这个主意不错
Yeah, that's pretty good.
我太喜欢了
I love it!
我会大叫  "抓到啦"
I'll be all like, "Busted!"
他们会说  "什么鬼"
And they'll be like, "What?!"
我们就一起说  "就是酱"
And then we'll all be like, "Oh, yeah!"
好好  我明白了
Yeah, I-I get it.
连我自己都不愿和我这种人亲热
I wouldn't make out with me, either.
这里有我拥有过的每一个收音机闹钟
In here is every clock radio I've ever owned.
计算器  录像带
Calculators, VHS tapes.
运动器材
Sporting equipment.
你还有运动器材啊
Y-You have sporting equipment?
那只是一个...高尔夫球
Well, oh, it's just a... it's a... A golf ball
我哥哥拿来砸我的头的
that my brother threw at my head.
砸下的坑现在还在呢
You can still feel the dent.
就在冰球留下的坑旁边
It's right next to the hockey puck dent.
你怎么还有一整盒的松果啊
Okay, why do you have a bin of pinecones?
这是我小时候收集的
I used to collect them as a child.
松果的鳞片螺旋的比例
The spiral of scales open in
按斐波那契列数排列
the Fibonacci sequence.
可当你把这事告诉你哥哥时
A fact that, when you tell your brother,
他会拿高尔夫球砸你脑袋
gets a golf ball thrown at your head.
那你为什么觉得有必要留下这些东西呢
So, why do you feel you need to save these things?
说好听点  这叫怀旧
I'd like to say it's nostalgia,
可实际是  每次我想扔掉某物时
but every time I think of throwing anything away,
我就会开始耳鸣
my ears start to ring,
内心忐忑得像有蝴蝶在我胃里乱飞
and I get butterflies in my stomach.
飞着飞着
And then it feels like
老鼠来了  蝴蝶被吃掉了
the butterflies get eaten by rats,
接下来  老鼠又被吃掉了...
and then, the-the rats get eaten by...
行了  我懂了  懂了
Okay. I get it. I get it.
最后来收尾的是恐龙
It ends with dinosaurs.
如果让你觉得瞧不起我  我很遗憾
I'm sorry if you think less of me.
我没有
I don't.
真的吗
Really?
因为我每次来这里
'Cause every time I come in here,
都会瞧不起自己
I think less of me.
为什么
Why?
因为我是个骗子
Because I'm a fraud.
我嘴上说自己意志强大
No. I purport to be a man of the mind.
还总念叨着会有科技大突破
I've been such a-a vocal champion of the singularity,
可一个要舍弃自己的身体
but how can I leave my body behind
成为网络一部分的我本人
and become one with the Internet
怎么能连一根牙刷都舍不得扔
when I've never even thrown a toothbrush away?
没关系  谢尔顿
It's okay, Sheldon.
我也有很多奇怪的东西不舍得扔掉
You know, I... I've saved a lot of weird things, too.
比如什么
Like what?
你知道我有一片显微镜玻片
Did you know I have a microscope slide
上面有一点点小组织
with a little bit of tissue
来自我第一个解剖的大脑
from the first brain I ever dissected?
我有一个旧泰迪熊
I have an old teddy bear
我偷偷用它擦了好多年鼻子
I secretly wiped my nose on for years.
这不是比赛
It's not a contest.
好  他们回来了
Okay, here they come.
藏起来
Go hide.
天了噜  等我出了柜
Oh, man, when I come out of the closet,
要把他们都干倒
I'm gonna nail those guys!
好  我听出哪里有歧义了  闭嘴
Yeah, I heard it. Shut up.
这是怎么回事
Hey, what's this?
听我说  我们干了件蠢事
Listen, we did a stupid thing.
我们跑去看了场电影  还撒了谎
We went to a movie and lied about it,
但我们知道错了
but we feel bad
想补偿你们
and want to make it up to you.
这花送给你们  你们要是不那么生气
So, these are for you, and if you're not too mad,
就赏个脸跟我们共进晚餐吧
we'd love to take you guys to dinner.
对  去哪儿吃都行
Yeah. Anywhere you want.
谢谢你们的坦诚
Well, thank you for being honest.
对  我本来想发火的
Yeah. You know, I want to be upset,
但我们做原型的确做得挺开心的
but we did kind of have fun working on the prototype.
别原谅他们  保持你们的怒气
Don't forgive them! Stay mad at them!
他在里面干嘛呢
What is he doing in there?
抓到你们咯
Busting you!
没关系  他们道歉了
It's okay. They apologized.
对  没事了
Yeah, it's fine.
这结局略显平淡啊
Well this is kind of anti-climactic.
你知道什么结局不平淡吗
You know what wasn't anti-climactic?
那电影的结局  听好了
The end of the movie. Get this.
不要剧透  不要剧透
No spoilers! No spoilers!
他又"进柜"了
And he's back in the closet.
去吃晚餐吧
Ready for dinner?
好呀
Yeah.
我们要不要叫上拉杰啊
Should we invite Raj?
要
Yes.
这事没有人知道吗
So, no one else knows about this?
只有你
Only you.
谢谢你信任我
Thank you for trusting me.
有女朋友的好处就是
What good is having a girlfriend
可以把自己的心理垃圾扔给她啊
if you can't unload your psychological sewage on her?
没错  我就是你的情绪茅坑
That's me, your emotional outhouse.
知道吗
You know,
如果某天你决定要处理这些东西
if you ever decide you want to do something about this,
我会陪着你
I'm-I'm here for you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我都不知道从哪下手好
I wouldn't even know how to begin.
一点点来吧
Baby steps, I guess.
我可以先试着把这高尔夫球扔掉
I suppose I could try getting rid of the golf ball.
好呀
Oh. Okay.
反正我脑袋上自带纪念"坑"了
I will always have the dent to remember it by.
你做到了
You did it.
感觉还好吗
Do you feel okay?
其实还可以
Actually, yes.
真的
I do.
我为你感到骄傲
Well, I'm proud of you.
谢谢
Oh. Thanks.
我很高兴把储藏仓库的事告诉了你
I'm glad I told you about the storage unit.
我现在感觉跟你更亲近了
Well, I feel closer to you now.
我也感觉跟你更亲近了
Oh, I feel closer to you, too.
话说
You know,
距离我上床睡觉的时间  还有几个小时呢
it's still a couple of hours until my bedtime.
你有什么想法吗
What did you have in mind?
你的容颜太惊人了
You look amazing.
这个分辨率  我跟你讲  绝了
I mean, this resolution is remarkable.
有必要为了这事赶我回家吗
I really had to go home for this?
有啊  感觉就像你就在我房里一样
Yes, but it's like you're right here in the room.
可是我并不在
And yet, I'm not.
感觉我一伸手就能碰到你
But I feel like I could reach out and touch you.
可是你并不能
And yet, you can't.
就是说啊
I know!